Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, 1957-1996 and undated
  - Writings by Others Subseries, ca. 1970-1994 and undated
    - Ellis, Gene, Poems (Box WO 6)
    - Elman, Richard, Poems (Box WO 6)
    - Elman, Richard, My Sweet Cheat Life In TV (Box WO 6)
    - Elliott, Lee, Betty Boles (Box WO 6)
    - Elzinga, Jeff, The Reunion (Box WO 6)
    - Emerson, Cornelia, Poems (Box WO 6)
    - Emerson, Nene, Vampire (Box WO 6)
    - England, David, Mannequins (Box WO 6)
    - Epps, Garrett, The Floating Island (Box WO 6)
    - Epps, Garrett, Short story (Box WO 6)
    - Evanson, Philip, Winton Churchill & the Sinews of Peace (Box WO 6)
    - Evans, Bob, 7-Minute Draft (Box WO 6)
    - Ewell, Catch A Falling Star (Box WO 6)
    - Favazza, Armando, Fellini: Analyst w/o Portfolio (Box WO 6)
    - Fetsko, Kathye, Harold (Box WO 6)
    - Finks, Richard, Short stories (Box WO 6)
    - Fische, Irene, Freeze Frame (Box WO 6)
    - Fitzpatrick, Nina, Fables of the Irish Intelligensia (Box WO 6)
    - Flynt, Candace, Sins of Omission (Box WO 6)
    - Foreman, Steve, Poems (Box WO 6)
    - Foret, Marguerite, The Forest of Flesh (Box WO 6)
    - Fowler, Albert, Fools Island (Box WO 6)
    - Foxworth, Bob, Hawk in the April Wind (Box WO 6)
    - Franklyn, A. Frderic, Keeno to Cannes: A Journey (Box WO 6)
    - Friedman, Robert S., Finale (Box WO 6)
    - Friedman, Robert S., In the Beginning (Box WO 6)
    - Fuermann, James, The New Year in Houston 1864 (Box WO 6)
    - Galbraith, Joyce, Poems (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Dog Love (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Hotel Malabar (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Poems (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, The Contemporary Poet & the Natural World (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Three Poets (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Atlantic Flyaway (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Poems (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Winter Oysters (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Sengekontacket Traveler (Box WO 6)
    - Galvin, Brendan, Never (Box WO 6)
    - Gamble, Roberta, Calhoun (Box WO 6)
    - Garnett, William M., Opus 23 in E Flat (Box WO 6)
    - Gates, Linda, The Thistle & the Rose (Box WO 6)
    - Gelfant, Blanche, Faulkner and Keats: The Ideality of Art In The Bear (Box WO 6)
    - Gelfman, Samuel, The Man From Beyond (Box WO 6)
    - Gelfman, Kay, Jake was Juggling Oranges (Box WO 6)
    - Geller, Bruce, Live Now, Pay Later: A Treatment (Box WO 7)
    - Gerhart, Mary & Anthony Yu, Morphologies of Faith: Essays on Religion & Culture in Honor of Nathan Scott Jr. (Box WO 7)
    - Geyer, Sandra Sue, To Whom It May Concern (Box WO 7)
    - Giardina, Denise, Storming Heaven (Box WO 7)
    - Gilbert, Jennifer, Book Review: Whistling in the Dark (Box WO 7)
    - Gibbons, Richard, Body & Soul (Box WO 7)
    - Gibson, Margaret, The Writing Teachers (Box WO 7)
    - Gibson, Dana, A Banker's Daughter (Box WO 7)
    - Gilbert, Craig, William Faulkner Project Script Draft (Box WO 7)
    - Gildner, Gary, A Week in South Dakota (Box WO 7)
    - Gingher, Robert, The Rough Road Home: Stories By NC Writers (Box WO 7)
    - Gingher, Robert, The Circle (Box WO 7)
    - Gioia, Dana, The Subculture of Poetry (Box WO 7)
    - Gioia, Dana, For the Birth of Christ (Box WO 7)
    - Gioia, Dana, Notes on the New Formalism (Box WO 7)
    - Goff, Paula, By Path's Coincedent (Box WO 7)
    - Goldsmith, Maurice Rev., Christmas Sermon (Box WO 7)
    - Goldstein, Laurence, A Letter to Andrew and Jonathan and other poems (Box WO 7)
    - Goll, Yvan, The Chaplinade (Box WO 7)
    - Gottlieb, Elaine, Short stories (Box WO 7)
    - Gottlieb, Elaine, The Woman Who Was Absent (Box WO 7)
    - Goyen, William, Recovering: Writing & Healing (Box WO 7)
    - Graham, John, The Writer's Voice (Box WO 7)
    - Greer, Ben, Patrick (Box WO 7)
    - Greiner, Donald, Emerson, Thoreau & Hemingway: Some Suggestions about Literary Heritage (Box WO 7)
    - Greiner, Donald, American Poets Since WWII (Box WO 7)
    - Green, Vincent S., Price of Victory: A Novel (Box WO 7)
    - Gwynn, R. S., The Drive-In (Box WO 7)
    - Gwynn, R. S., The Narcissiad (Box WO 7)
    - Gwynn, R. S., The Age of Narcissus (Box WO 7)
    - Haasse, Hella, The Scarlet City (Box WO 7)
    - Hagy, Alyson, Madonna on her Back: Stories (Box WO 7)
    - Hagy, Alyson, Where Men Go To Cry (Box WO 7)
    - Hall, James B., Old Man Finds What Was Lost (Box WO 7)
    - Hammond, J., Bilo Blues (Box WO 7)
    - Hammond, Jerold, Say Hi! to God! (Box WO 7)
    - Hammond, Jerry, Review of Field of Dreams (Box WO 7)
    - Hammond, Jerry, Miscellaneous poems and short stories (Box WO 7)
    - Hammond, Jerry, Fights Tonight-Prufrock At Wasteland Arena (Box WO 7)
    - Hammond, Essay (Box WO 7)
    - Hammond, J. S., Untitled story (Box WO 7)
    - Hampton, Mary, Transformations in Heroic Discourse in Shakespeare and Marlow (Box WO 7)
    - Handel, Elizabeth, Poems (Box WO 7)
    - Hankla, Cathryn, The Strawberry Patch (Box WO 7)
    - Hankla, Cathryn, First Person Love (Box WO 7)
    - Hankla, Cathryn, Skeleton (Box WO 7)
    - Hardison, O. B., 3 Types of Renaissance Catharsis (Box WO 8)
    - Hardison, Afternoon Meditation of G. B. R. (Box WO 8)
    - Harris, Barbara, The Lady With a Taste For Fiction (Box WO 8)
    - Harris, Marina, A Night Friend (Box WO 8)
    - Harris, Marina, A Gift (Box WO 8)
    - Harvard, John, Death of a Shop Teacher (Box WO 8)
    - Harvard, John M., The Return of Alice to Wonderland (Box WO 8)
    - Harvard, John M., Third Grade Justice (Box WO 8)
    - Harvard, John M., Death of the Princeton Owl (Box WO 8)
    - Harwich, Lynne, Swap Night (Box WO 8)
    - Harzo, T. A., The Two Faces of Matt Donelson (Box WO 8)
    - Haysom, Elizabeth, Poems (Box WO 8)
    - Healy, Eloise, Poems (Box WO 8)
    - Health, William, Poems and short stories (Box WO 8)
    - Hemley, Robin, Turning Life Into Fiction (Box WO 8)
    - Henry, DeWitt, Witness (Box WO 8)
    - Henry, DeWitt, The Marriage of Anna Maye Potts (Box WO 8)
    - Henry, DeWitt, The Novels of Brian Moore (Box WO 8)
    - Henry, DeWitt, At Home (Box WO 8)
    - Herzig, Jack, Amnesia and Solitaire (Box WO 8)
    - Herzig, Jack, Short stories (Box WO 8)
    - Hickland, Austin, We Unburthened Crawl (Box WO 8)
    - Hicklin, Robert, Synopsis of We Unburthened Crawl and The Brutality of Stone (Box WO 8)
    - Hillard, Richard, The Winnowing Star (Box WO 8)
    - Hillard, Richard, My Brother, Death (Box WO 8)
    - Hillman, Jacques, Review of That's What I Like About the South (Box WO 8)
    - Hlavsa, James, Faulkner and the Thoroughly Modern Novel (Box WO 8)
    - Hinrickes, Tom, 15th Summer Writing Workshop (Box WO 8)
    - Hodges, Harriet, Narcissa (Box WO 8)
    - Hoffman, Daniel, After the Quarry (Box WO 8)
    - Hood, Mary, Nobody's Fool, After Moore, and Desire Call of the Wild Hen (Box WO 8)
    - Horvath, Brooke, Consolation of Ground Zero (Box WO 8)
    - Horvath, Brooke, Miscellaneous poems (Box WO 8)
    - Houston, Robert, Invasion of the Bodice Rippers (Box WO 8)
    - Howes, Barbara, Myself (Box WO 8)
    - Hoy, Pat C., A Mosaic of Southern Masculinity (Box WO 8)
    - Hubbard, Bitt, English notebook (Box WO 8)
    - Huddle, David, Notebook (Box WO 8)
    - Huddle, David, Contra Nauseam (Box WO 8)
    - Huddle, David, The Front Yard (Box WO 8)
    - Huff, Robert, Trio (Box WO 8)
    - Huebues, Bernard, Poems (Box WO 8)
    - Huey, Tom, You Could Not Let Me Go (Box WO 8)
    - Huey, Tommy, Pompeii (Box WO 8)
    - Hummer, T. R., Poems (Box WO 8)
    - Humphries, Jefferson, On the Inevitability of Theory in Southern Literary (Box WO 8)
    - Hunter, Marsha, Poems (Box WO 8)
    - Ignotus, Miles, The Writer In A Hotwired Democracy (Box WO 8)
    - Jacobs, Lucky, Fragment. from dissertation (Box WO 8)
    - Juass, David, Glossolalia (Box WO 8)
    - Jacobson, Jane, Untitled story (Box WO 8)
    - Jacobson, Jane, The Well of the Seven Lambs (Box WO 8)
    - Janiszewski, Steven, Guacamole Tostada, (2 folders) (Box WO9)
    - Janiszewski, Steven, It's Only Natural and The Second Tuesday (Box WO9)
    - Jaro, Benita, The Key, the Lock, the Door in the Wall, (2 folders) (Box WO9)
    - Jason, Philip, Biography of Brendan Galvin (Box WO9)
    - Jauss, David, Articles of Faith (Box WO9)
    - Johnson, B.S., Poems 2 (Box WO9)
    - Johnson, Larry, Veins (Box WO9)
    - Johnson, Larry, Poems (Box WO9)
    - Johnson, Mary, Poems (Box WO9)
    - Jones, Edward, Island (Box WO9)
    - Jones, James, Epigraphs and letter (Box WO9)
    - Joyce, William, Poems (Box WO9)
    - Joynes, St. Leger M., Under the Coat, Please (Box WO9)
    - Kachman, Geneva, Mistress of Fine Arts Initial Examination (Box WO9)
    - Kafka, Kimberly, Come Like Shadows (Box WO9)
    - Kafka, Kim, Keeping it where the Sun Doesn't Shine (Box WO9)
    - Katzenbach, Maria, Short stories (Box WO9)
    - Katzenbach, Maria, Naming the Enemy (Box WO9)
    - Keeble, John, Yellowfish (Box WO9)
    - Kelly, C. Brian, Muskrat Guilt (Box WO9)
    - Kempf, Elizabeth, Poems (Box WO9)
    - Kempf, Elizabeth, Euphemia (Box WO9)
    - Kempowski, Walter, Dog Days, chapters 36-40 (Box WO9)
    - Kendrick, Stephen, Intro 8 notebook (Box WO9)
    - Keyser, Earl, Poems (Box WO9)
    - Kibler, James E., Review of My Silk Purse and Yours (Box WO9)
    - Kimber, Bob, To Grandmother's House We Go (Box WO9)
    - King, Lee, Poems (Box WO9)
    - King, Leyland, Song of My Son (Box WO9)
    - King, Leyland, Poems (Box WO9)
    - Kingbury, Celia, Renaissance Laughter (Box WO9)
    - Kline, Christina Baker, Sweet Water (Box WO 17)
    - Kooser, Ted, A Few Attractive Strangers (Box WO 9)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Teaching and the Non-Standard Writer (Box WO 9)
    - Kreisworth, Martin, Centers, Openings, and Endings: Some Faulknesian Constants (Box WO 9)
    - Lakehomer, Leona, Poems (Box WO 9)
    - La Couras, Pete, Short stories (Box WO 9)
    - Lamont, Nathan Bedford Forrest, Tom Lamarr (Box WO 9)
    - Lander Paul, Written Away from the Fire (Box WO 9)
    - Lang, John, Essay on Fred Chappell's Moments of Light (Box WO 9)
    - Langbaum, Robert, The Revolving Bookstand... and Autobiography and Myth in 'Out of Africa' (Box WO 9)
    - Lardner, Ted, Bathing in the Rio Grande (Box WO 9)
    - Larkin, David, The Eternal Family Settles a Question (Box WO 9)
    - LaRiche, William, Almost Alright? (Box WO 9)
    - Larson, Clinton, Poems (Box WO 9)
    - LaSalle, Pete, Dolphin Dreaming (Box WO 9)
    - LaSalle, Peter, A Guide to Some Small, Border Airports (Box WO 9)
    - LaSalle, Peter, A Theory of Dentistry and Port-au-Prince (Box WO 9)
    - Lawrence, Starling, Reunion (Box WO 9)
    - Layman, Richard, How to Read John Dos Passos' 'Number 1' (Box WO 9)
    - Leary, D.A., So He Came Down (Box WO 9)
    - Leon, Poems (Box WO 9)
    - Leonard, John, Portrait of the First Novelist as a Loser (Box WO 9)
    - Levkoff, Michael, Notes from Garrett's English 56 class (Box WO 9)
    - Lewis, J.D., Lying on Bed (Box WO 9)
    - Lindensmith, Mark, Short-Term Losses (Box WO 10)
    - Lipinsky, Mike, Short story fragment (Box WO 10)
    - Lish, Gordon, Zimzum (Box WO 10)
    - Lish, Gordon, A Kind of Magnificence (Box WO 10)
    - Little, John, Sunday Beer (Box WO 10)
    - Long, Kate, Prologue to Ordinaries (Box WO 10)
    - Longley, John Lewis, End of Season (Box WO 10)
    - Longley, John, Gentle, Into that Good Night, (3 folders) (Box WO 10)
    - Longley, Judy, My Journey Towards You (Box WO 10)
    - Longley, Judy, Poems (Box WO 10)
    - Lopez, Minerva, Essay on In the Labrinthe (Box WO 10)
    - Lottman, Maryrica, The Dog-Walker (Box WO 10)
    - Loughran, Joseph, Stand the Champion (Box WO 10)
    - Low, David, Short story (Box WO 10)
    - Lowe, Keith, Undercurrents (Box WO 10)
    - Loyd, Marianne, Poems (Box WO 10)
    - Lucid, Robert, Anecdotes and Recollections (Box WO 10)
    - Luschei, Glenna, Mayflower Van Lines (Box WO 10)
    - Lyll, Jenkins, Like Mango Trees (Box WO 10)
    - Lyne, Barbara with Mary Wolcott and Katherine Wootus, For Lovers Only (Box WO 10)
    - Macauley, Robie and Van der Leun, If... (Box WO 10)
    - Madden, David, Wright Morris' 'In Orbit': An Unbroken Series of Poetic Gestures (Box WO 10)
    - Magun, Carol, Circling Eden (Box WO 10)
    - Maiolo, Joeseph, Man of Letters, (2 folders) (Box WO 10)
    - Maiolo, Joe, Poem (Box WO 10)
    - Maiolo, Joe, Gloria's Day in the Pasture (Box WO 10)
    - Maiolo, Joe, Review of The Magic Striptease (Box WO 10)
    - Mallon, Thomas, Henry and Clara (Box WO 10)
    - Malm, Ira, Review of Jean Stafford's The Interior Castle (Box WO 10)
    - Mann, James, Vandal (Box WO 10)
    - Massey, D.K., The Guard Tower (Box WO 10)
    - Masters, Hilary, A Stray Shot (Box WO 10)
    - Masters, Hilary, Death of an Editor (Box WO 10)
    - Masters, Hilary, What Writer's Block? (Box WO 10)
    - Masters, Hilary, A Hand for the Python (Box WO 10)
    - Masters, Hilary, Last Stands, (2 folders) (Box WO 10)
    - Masters, Hilary, Connections (Box WO 10)
    - Masters, Hilary, Success, (2 folders) (Box WO 10)
    - May, Naomi, A Place to Sleep, Reconciliation, A Greek Facade, Exchanges, and Chapter 1 (Box WO 11)
    - Mayo, Michael, Jones and the Old Man (Box WO 11)
    - Matson, Katinka, Alice, Observation, and Entry (Box WO 11)
    - Matzke, Mary Frances, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - Mazzaro, Jerome, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - McAuley, James J., Cullen's Loss (Box WO 11)
    - McAuley, James, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - McAuley, James, After the Blizzard (Box WO 11)
    - McBuilkin, Frank, Rufus Brillingham: Tragedy of the Farm (Box WO 11)
    - McCall, Herbert, Untitled story (Box WO 11)
    - McCloskey, Mark, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - McCollins, William, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - McCorkle, Jill, July 7: A Novel, (2 folders) (Box WO 11)
    - McCullough, F.W., The Music (Box WO 11)
    - McCullough, Frank, The Night They Got Agnew (Box WO 11)
    - McDougall, Jo, The Woman in the Next Booth (Box WO 11)
    - McFee, Michael, Prospectus (Box WO 11)
    - McGlassom, Nancy, Untitled story (Box WO 11)
    - McGonigle, Tom, Reviews (Box WO 11)
    - McGonigle, Tom, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - McGonigle, Thomas, The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov (Box WO 11)
    - McGonigle, Thomas, The Pastures of Stupidity and The Testimonial Dinner (Box WO 11)
    - McGovern, P.A., Going Home (Box WO 11)
    - McHaney, Tom, The Shoplifter (Box WO 11)
    - McHaney, Tom, The Death of the Fox (Box WO 11)
    - McHaney, Tom, 'Sanctuary' and Frazer's Slain Kings (Box WO 11)
    - McMillen, Excerpt from book (Box WO 11)
    - McQuilkin, Frank, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - Meriwether, James, What Happens When You Eat Magnolias? (Box WO 11)
    - Meriwether, James, Dashes in Hemingway's 'A Farewell to Arms' (Box WO 11)
    - Meriwether, James, Notes on Textual History of 'The Sound and the Fury' (Box WO 11)
    - Meriwether, James, Prefatory Note by Faulkner for Compson Appendix (Box WO 11)
    - Mewshaw, Mike, Waking Slow (Box WO 11)
    - Mewshaw, Mike, Untitled, (2 folders) (Box WO 11)
    - Miles, Elizabeth, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - Miles, Jack, Economics and Politics of Book Reviewing (Box WO 11)
    - Miller, Vassar, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - Miller, Vassar, Pact (Box WO 11)
    - Miller, Vassar, False Spring (Box WO 11)
    - Milligan, Thomas, Poems and an autobiographical sketch (Box WO 11)
    - Millman, Larry, King of Beasts (Box WO 11)
    - Millman, Larry, Neanderthals (Box WO 11)
    - Millman, Lawrence, The Book of Origins (Box WO 11)
    - Millman, Lawrence, The Ballad of Hero Jesse, (2 folders) (Box WO 11)
    - Millman, Lawrence, Short stories (Box WO 11)
    - Millman, Lawrence, Moon/Snail/Sonata (Box WO 11)
    - Millman, Lawrence, Smell of Earth and Clay: Greenlandic Charms, Spells, and Songs (Box WO 11)
    - Mills, Wil, Poems (Box WO 11)
    - Millstein, Stuart, Two for Tea, Bubble Bath, From House to House, and other poems (Box WO 11)
    - Moffett, Judy, Poems, (2 folders) (Box WO 12)
    - Montgomery, Marion, The Country, Here (Box WO 12)
    - Moore, Elizabeth, Pearls and Ash, (2 folders) (Box WO 12)
    - Moore, Harold, The Perfect Hi-Fi and The Incident at Billy Springs (Box WO 12)
    - Moore, J.R., Some Night Thoughts on Beckett (Box WO 12)
    - Moore, Richard, Poems (Box WO 12)
    - Moore, Richard, A Question of Survival, (2 folders) (Box WO 12)
    - Moore, Richard, The No Self, the Little Self, and the Poets (Box WO 12)
    - Morris, John S., And the Sun (Box WO 12)
    - Morris, Robert, The Poet Comes Home (Box WO 12)
    - Morrison, Markesan, The Knee-Kisser (Box WO 12)
    - Moorman, David, Scale: A Preview (Box WO 12)
    - Moxley, Joseph, Creative Writing in America (Box WO 12)
    - Mueller, Craig, Marlowe, then Shakespeare, then Jonson (Box WO 12)
    - Mulholland, Paige E., So You Want to Achieve Excellence (Box WO 12)
    - Musing, Sandra, George Garrett: A Bibliography (Box WO 12)
    - Myers, Lucas, The Feral Girl (Box WO 12)
    - Myers, Lucas, Two plays (Box WO 12)
    - Myers, Lucas, Poems (Box WO 12)
    - Myers, Lucas, Ah, Youth... (Box WO 12)
    - Napoli, Donna Jo, Stories (Box WO 12)
    - Nassar, Eugene, Both God and Fake (Box WO 12)
    - Nesbitt, Paula, Sky Child (Box WO 12)
    - Nicholson, Jacques, Justin Revisited (Box WO 12)
    - Nims, John Frederick, Zany in Denim (Box WO 12)
    - Noertker, Joseph, Transit of Jordan (Box WO 12)
    - O'Connell, Richard, Translation of Irish monastic poems (Box WO 12)
    - O'Connor, Sarah, Exiled: A Memoir (Box WO 12)
    - O'Connor, Tom, Edmund Campion, S.J. (Box WO 12)
    - Orlee, Jacqueline, Juliet of the Spirits (Box WO 12)
    - Palmer, Bryan, Somewhere Through the Wilderness (Box WO 12)
    - Palmer, Bryan, The Only Way (Box WO 12)
    - Parker, Michael, Hello Down There, (2 folders) (Box WO 12)
    - Parks, Brad, Getting People Hurt (Box WO 12)
    - Parks, Sarah, In Orbit (Box WO 12)
    - Patrick, W.B., Poems (Box WO 12)
    - Pawlowski, Robert, The Poetry of Wallace Stevens and Myth as Metaphor (Box WO 12)
    - Peck, John, Letting Up (Box WO 12)
    - Peden, William, Queenie's Pups, Date Palms and Coliseum, and Absent Thee from Felicity (Box WO 12)
    - Peden, William, review of Garrett's Maggots in the Basement and The Blue Slipper (Box WO 12)
    - Peden, William, The Cross-Country Dog (Box WO 12)
    - Peden, William, Fragments from the Workbook of an Obscure Writer (Box WO 12)
    - Peet, James M., Modern Light on the Soul (Box WO 12)
    - Peet, Mel, Dwight MacDonald or Politics, (5 folders) (Box WO 12)
    - Penick, Douglas, Chinese Nights (Box WO 12)
    - Penick, D.J., The Conquest of Mexico (Box WO 12)
    - Perkins, D.A., The Ancient Book of Ancient Time (Box WO 12)
    - Perry, Laurie Lynn, A Collection of Poems (Box WO 12)
    - Peter, Emmett, review of Poison Pen (Box WO 12)
    - Petracca, Joseph, The Proud Rebel (Box WO 12)
    - Pfeil, Fred, MLA and Poker Fugue (Box WO 13)
    - Pickerel, Paul, Prints of critical literary essays (Box WO 13)
    - Pierson, Amanda, Dancing on Water (Box WO 13)
    - Pierson, Mandy, Relative Terms, Consolation, and other stories (Box WO 13)
    - Ponder, Dulane, Poems (Box WO 13)
    - Ponder, Leanne, Poems (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Poems, (5 folders) (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Bag Ladies Never Beg (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Voyages (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, A Game (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Worms and Water (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Intro to Poetry (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Deceiving the Worms (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, The Purity of Diction in O.B. Hardison's Verse (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Blackbird (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Surrounded by Dangerous Things (Box WO 13)
    - Poster, Carol, Poems of Jacques Prevert, (2 folders) (Box WO 13)
    - Price, Reynolds, A Long and Happy Life (Box WO 13)
    - Preston, D.S., Narrow Passage and Chatham (Box WO 13)
    - Prunty, Wyatt, The Distance into Place (Box WO 13)
    - Prunty, Wyatt, Allegory to Causality: Robert Lowell's Poetic Shift (Box WO 13)
    - Pryse, Marjorie, Proposal and request for fellowship (Box WO 13)
    - Purviance, Donald, Little Seizures, (2 folders) (Box WO 13)
    - Purviance, Donald, Dead Giveaway (Box WO 13)
    - Quigley, Peter, Roasted Chestnuts at Christmas (Box WO 13)
    - Ramsey, Paul, The Naming of Adam (Box WO 13)
    - Randall, Nora, Poems (Box WO 13)
    - Rath, Roger, The Model and Trailers (Box WO 13)
    - Raun, Timothy, Anger Unfinished (Box WO 13)
    - Ray, David, You Can't Go Home Again, You Sonofabitch! (Box WO 13)
    - Ray, David, Poems (Box WO 13)
    - Real, Jere, VQR is Varied (Box WO 13)
    - Reddick, Tom, Excerpts from Whose Bright Stars? (Box WO 13)
    - Reed, Kit, Outline for revision (Box WO 13)
    - Reed, Kit, Florida on my Mind (Box WO 13)
    - Reed, Kit, Oblivion is a ... (Box WO 13)
    - Rees, Ennis, Poems ( folder) (Box WO 13)
    - Rees, Ennis, In the Dallas Airport (Box WO 13)
    - Reist, John, Poetry of Permanent Things (Box WO 13)
    - Reiter, Thomas, Poems (Box WO 13)
    - Reiter, Thomas, At a Nephew's Grave and A Moment of Geese (Box WO 13)
    - Rigsbee, David, Ratio: poems (Box WO 13)
    - Robinson, Phil Alden, Field of Dreams (Box WO 13)
    - Robinson, William, Description of an anthology of essays on movies (Box WO 13)
    - Rodenbeck, Jon von B., The Voyeurs (Box WO 13)
    - Roemer, Jackie, Sweet (Box WO 13)
    - Rollyson, Carl, Rebecca West at 100: A Saga of the Century (Box WO 13)
    - Rooney, Andrew, Paradise Person and Walter Stukowski: Reg'lar Guy (Box WO 13)
    - Roper, John, Foreword to bio of Howard Kester and a report on the series of bios (Box WO 13)
    - Rosen, Ken, Mountains, etc. (Box WO 13)
    - Rosen, Kenneth, The Giant Day (Box WO 13)
    - Ross, Jean W., Biography of John Cheever (Box WO 13)
    - Rubin, Louis, The Literary Attacks on Styron's 'Nat Turner' (Box WO 13)
    - Rubin, Louis, Notes on a Rear-Guard Action (Box WO 13)
    - Rubin, Louis, Grant proposals (Box WO 13)
    - Ruffin, Paul, The Mosquito (Box WO 13)
    - Ruffin, Paul, The Man Who Would Be God (Box WO 14)
    - Ruffin, Paul, Book Reviewing in Texas (Box WO 14)
    - Ruffin, Paul, Our Women (Box WO 14)
    - Ruffin, Paul, The Mosquito (Box WO 14)
    - Russell, Peter, Miscellaneous writings (Box WO 14)
    - Ryan, Richard, To Aesop (Box WO 14)
    - Sage, Norman, Seven Blackberries (Box WO 14)
    - St. Clair, Jeffrey, Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Sanders, Scott Russell, Review of The Succession for Chicago Sun Times (Box WO 14)
    - Sanders, Scott, Book Week review of The Succession (Box WO 14)
    - Sanders, Scott, The First Journey of Jason Moss (Box WO 14)
    - Sandy, Stephen, Poems, (3 folders) (Box WO 14)
    - Sandy, Stephen, Essay on Theodore Holmes (Box WO 14)
    - Sandy, Stephen, Flight of Steps (Box WO 14)
    - Sandy, Stephen, Experienced Bards (Box WO 14)
    - Saunders, Budd, They Ain't Got No Respect (Box WO 14)
    - Sawicki, Phillip, It's Art (Box WO 14)
    - Schabert, Ina, Report, (2 folders) (Box WO 14)
    - Scherman, Peter, Cliffs of Clay (Box WO 14)
    - Scholes, Robert, Afterword on Vonnegut (Box WO 14)
    - Schuster, Alberta, So What Did You Learn at School Today? (Box WO 14)
    - Scott, Carolyne, Good-bye, Hello Joe (Box WO 14)
    - Scott, Nathan, The Poetry of Richard Wilbur (Box WO 14)
    - Scott, Nathan, Poetry and Prayer (Box WO 14)
    - Scott, Nathan A., Jr., The New 'Trahison des Clercs' (Box WO 14)
    - Sears, Patricia, The Girl in the Black Raincoat (Box WO 14)
    - Seay, James, Does Anyone wanna Buy My Little Brother? (Box WO 14)
    - Seferis, George, Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Seligmann, Nancy, Thought-Sex (Box WO 14)
    - Seshachari, Neila C., 'F' is for Fugitive (Box WO 14)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, Cage of Bone (Box WO 17)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, An Inquiry into the Teaching of Writing as an Art (Box WO 14)